A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Projects, Series L FA348
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Miscellaneous (A-Z), 1959-1971 (Box 222, Folder 2249)
  NAR appeals referred to Rockefeller Brothers Fund. Most appeals declined. NAR interest in special Rockefeller Brother Fund projects.
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Contributions, 1955-1970 (Box 222, Folder 2250)
  Rockefeller Brothers Fund contributions made because of special NAR interest.
- Rockefeller Brothers Fund - Raymon Magsaysay Award Foundation, 1957-1968 (Box 222, Folder 2251)
  Instruction, organization, and operation. NAR and John Davison Rockefeller 3rd special interests.
- Rockefeller Family (A-D), 1945-1971 (Box 222, Folder 2252)
  Appeals to family members. Requests for information about family members and genealogical facts. Previous to 1960 discarded. Letters of appreciation for family philanthropies. Requests for photos of John Davison Rockefeller, Jr. NAR invited to join Parke Society in 1963 and attend meetings in 1964 and 1968; declined. Requests for information on Rockefeller family, genealogy. Letters climing relationship to Rockefeller family. Miscellaneous correspondence with Rockefeller family members. David Stokes article, "The Rockefeller Dynasty," 1968. Requests for information on Rockefeller family and possible relationships. "El Mundo," San Juan, articles on Rockefeller activites, 1957.
- Rockefeller Family (E-J), 1945-1971 (Box 222, Folder 2253)
- Rockefeller Family (K-O), 1945-1971 (Box 223, Folder 2254)
- Rockefeller Family (P-R), 1945-1971 (Box 223, Folder 2255)
- Rockefeller Family (S-Z), 1945-1971 (Box 223, Folder 2256)
- Rockefeller Family Fund (A-Z), 1969 (Box 224, Folder 2257)
  Miscellaneous. Correspondence re Bar Harbor Festival, donation. Scrivner's letter to Fr. Devaney re OXFAM.
- Rockefeller Foundation - General, 1941-1955 (Box 224, Folder 2258)
  NAR comments on Rockefeller Foundation program. Relations with Rockefeller Foundation officers.
- Rockefeller Foundation (A-C), 1947-1971 (Box 224, Folder 2259)
  Appeals made to NAR referred to Rockefeller Foundation, Rockefeller Foundation disposition of appeals. Criticisms of the Rockefeller Foundation. Letter from David Rockefeller about archives establishment.
- Rockefeller Foundation (D-K), 1947-1971 (Box 224, Folder 2260)
- Rockefeller Foundation (L-Q), 1947-1971 (Box 224, Folder 2261)
- Rockefeller Foundation (R-Z), 1947-1971 (Box 224, Folder 2262)
  Appeals made to NAR referred to Rockefeller Foundation, Rockefeller Foundation disposition of appeals. Criticisms of the Rockefeller Foundation.
- Rockefeller Public Service Awards, 1955-1961 (Box 224, Folder 2263)
  Awards were established under a grant from John Davison Rockefeller 3rd and are administered by the Woodrow Wilson School of Public and Internal Affairs of Princeton University. Letter re this award made for distinguished public service. Available only to employees of the Federal Government.
- Rockefeller-Spelman Family, 1962-1964 (Box 224, Folder 2264)
  Newspaper clipping concerning the Harvey Spelman House in Akron. Inquiry about the Spelman Foundation.
- Rockefeller University - General Correspondence/Miscellaneous File, 1947-1971 (Box 225, Folder 2265)
  NAR neither an officer nor trustee of Rockefeller University. Memo re Rockefeller University and Cornell negotiating with New York City for air rights over FDR Drive for purposes of expansion. Correspondence re F. Cartier's drawing of Rockefeller Institute, 1969. Booklet, "Interaction between Man, Earth & Universe," 1968. Study on autistic children by Lorn Wing. Correspondence re dissatisfaction with care received at Rockefeller University Hospital.
- Rockefeller University - General Correspondence/Miscellaneous File, 1947-1971 (Box 225, Folder 2265A)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted - Confidential material.
- Rockefeller University - Apartments and Property, 1971 (Box 225, Folder 2266)
  Miscellaneous correspondence. (No NAR connection with Rockefeller University or the Sutton Terrace apartment building.)
- Rockefeller University - Printed Matter, 1953-1971 (Box 225, Folder 2267)
- Root, Oren, 1950-1971 (Box 225, Folder 2268)
  Appointed Superintendent of Banks in 1961 by NAR, resigned 3/17/64.
- Rosenberg, Anna M. - General Correspondence, 1936-1971 (Box 225, Folder 2269)
  (Mrs. Paul G. Hoffman.) Labor Consultant. Miscellaneous correspondence and clippings. Copy of Report on Government's Inter-Agency Fertilizer Program, 12/21/47. Executive order establishing the Office of Defense Transportation in the Executive Office of the President and defining its functions and duties. Statement by Senator William Benton (D-Conn.) in praise of Anna M. Rosenberg inserted in "Congressional Record," 12/21/50. An explanation of the Rheingold Health & Welfare Program for Employees and Their Families. Anna M. Rosenberg received Horatio Alger Award for Successful Career, 7/8/49. Pan American Society Dinner/Public Service Record, 1947. First American citizen to receive Medal of Freedom, 1945.
- Rosenberg, Anna M. - Profile of Anna Rosenberg, 1936 (Box 225, Folder 2270)
- Rosenberg, Anna M. - Address by Maurice P. Davidson, 1940 (Box 225, Folder 2271)
  Address delivered over the radio at Mexico City re the Inauguration of President Avila Camacho, 12/6/40.
- Rostow, W. W., Dr., 1955-1959 (Box 225, Folder 2272)
  "The Stages of Economic Growth and the Problems of Peaceful Co-Existence." Personal notes. NAR praises memo on American program of action and work in India.
- Rotary Clubs, General, 1950-1969 (Box 225, Folder 2273)
  Letter of 8/26/69 requesting assistance from the Rockefeller Foundation in connection with establishment of Health Communities in Rotary Clubs. Invitations by Rotary Clubs.
- Ruhr Plans, 1947 (Box 225, Folder 2274)
  Robert Moses' article on the Ruhr. NAR's thanks.
- Ruml, Beardsley, 1936-1960 (Box 225, Folder 2275)
  Personal notes and business correspondence. Copies of Beadsley Ruml's talks and papers.
- Sa-Sh, 1941-1971 (Box 226, Folder 2276)
  Alexander Sachs' proposed study of economic and national security, NAR decides not to support him, 1955. Production since 1900, from the Conference Board Business Record, 1955. Correspondence re A. V. Sack's book "Alfred Nobel: The Giant of Vision." Correspondence with Sabastao Sampaio, Former Brazilian Ambassador to Mexico, in charge of strong Brazilian Confederation of Commercial Associations, 1949. Offers of art work. Walter Smith (Alfred E. Smith's son) appeals for financial aid. Foreign Consular Representatives in Cleveland, Ohio, from Mrs. M. A. de Sperry. Address before the Pennsylvania Society of Sons of the Revolution by H. W. Prentis, Jr., 4/3/51. World Institute report from Julius Steelman, 12/29/41.
- Si-So, 1941-1971 (Box 226, Folder 2277)
- Sp-Sz, 1941-1971 (Box 226, Folder 2278)
- Saint Faith's House, 1947-1951 (Box 227, Folder 2279)
  Appeal declined by NAR at first. Mrs. Laurance Spelman Rockefeller and others in family contribute. Mrs. Laurance Spelman Rockefeller is vice president and board member. NAR contribution in 1951.
- Salt Water Distillation, 1956-1958 (Box 227, Folder 2280)
  Rolf Eliasson paper, "Economics of Desalting Brackish Waters," 9/18/58. "A Possible Positive Move In the Middle East," 11/6/57. Correspondence and clipping re "De-salting Process."
- San Francisco Bay Area - Westbay Community Associates, 1967 (Box 227, Folder 2281)
  Mrs. Leslie Mayne writes NAR re conservation and David Rockefeller's proposal for development of a "City in the Bay" off Burlingame-San Mateo shoreline. NAR nor involved in this project.
- Save the Children Federation - General Correspondence, 1960 (Box 227, Folder 2282)
  Request for aid and background on San Carlos Work Camp Project, 1960.
- Scherbak, H., 1948-1950 (Box 227, Folder 2283)
  Suggestions to improve on democratic system, other plans, ackowledgements.
- Scholarship Requests (A-Z), 1970 (Box 227, Folder 2284)
- Schools, Miscellaneous, 1960-1971 (Box 227, Folder 2285)
  Requests for financial support.
- Schools - Foreign (American) Schools, 1960-1971 (Box 227, Folder 2286)
  Previous to 1960 discarded. Requests for financial aid.
- Schools - Miscellaneous, Alabama - Mississippi, 1948-1971 (Box 227, Folder 2287)
  Requests for financial assistance.
- Schools - Maine, Skowhegan School of Painting & Sculpture, 1950-1971 (Box 227, Folder 2288)
  NAR $100 donations made in 1950, 1951, 1968, 1969, 1971. Founding sponsor. Membership in Skowhegan Four Hundred.
- Schools - Maine, Skowhegan School of Painting & Sculpture - Report, 1965 (Box 227, Folder 2289)
- Schools - Maryland, Stevenson, St. Timothy's School, 1961-1971 (Box 228, Folder 2290)
  NAR contribution to the St. Timothy's Latin American Seminar, 1971. NAR contribution, 1961. Miscellaneous information on School's programs, donation requests, etc.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Springfield, Macduffie School for Girls, 1963 (Box 228, Folder 2291)
  NAR contribution of $5,000.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Boston, New England Conservatory of Music, 1952-1959 (Box 228, Folder 2292)
  NAR's support of student violinist Asyton Pinto. Exchange Student Project.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Deerfield, Deerfield Academy - Building Fund, 1956-1964 (Box 228, Folder 2294)
  "Fund Raising Potentials for Deerfield Academy." Requests for funds, appreciation letters to contributors.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Deerfield, Deerfield Academy - Luncheons for Dr. Frank Boyden, 1949-1955 (Box 228, Folder 2295)
  Lists of those accepting and regretting retained. Letters discarded.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Deerfield, Deerfield Academy - Luncheons for Dr. Frank Boyden - Luncheon 12/6/55 for Dr. Boyden, 1955 (Box 228, Folder 2296)
  Lists retained. Acceptances and regrets discarded.
- Schools - Massachusetts, Deerfield, Deerfield Academy - General Correspondence, 1948-1971 (Box 228, Folder 2297)
  Booklets. Frank Boyden, Headmaster 1902-1968. 1949 Mr. Elliot's speech at Deerfield.
- Schools - New Hampshire, New Jersey, New Mexico, 1954-1970 (Box 229, Folder 2298)
  NAR contribution to St. Paul's School, Concord, New Hampshire, 1956. NAR contribution to the Peck School, Morristown, New Jersey, 1962. General requests for aid.
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - General, 1952-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2299)
  Various requests for contributions. NAR contributed $62,870.94 between 1952 and 1963. Correspondents include Laurance Spelman Rockefeller.
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - General, 1952-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2299A)
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - Pledge, Music Building, 1959 (Box 229, Folder 2300)
  NAR gift of Standard Oil stock, $50,927.19 in 1959. Additional contributions from John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Laurance Spelman Rockefeller, NAR: $200,000.
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - Pledge, Music Building, 1959 (Box 229, Folder 2300A)
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - Printed Matter, 1970-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2301)
- Schools - New Hampshire, Exeter, Phillips Exeter Academy - Financial Reports, 1970-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2302)
- Schools - New Jersey, 1946 (Box 229, Folder 2303)
  Admiral Farragut Academy of Florida and New Jersey. Offer to NAR to become member of the Board of Advisors; declined.
- Schools - New York State, 1953-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2304)
  NAR contribution to State Training School for Boys, 1967. Miscellaneous requests for aid.
- Schools - New York State - Albany Academy, 1963-1969 (Box 229, Folder 2305)
  NAR contributions, 1963, 1969.
- Schools - New York State - Mill Neck, Mill Neck Manor Lutheran School for the Deaf, 1960-1969 (Box 229, Folder 2306)
  Miscellaneous correspondence. No financial requests.
- Schools - New York State - Tarrytown, Public and Parochial Schools, Board of Education, 1962-1971 (Box 229, Folder 2307)
  NAR donation to Marymount College, 1969. Miscellaneous requests for financial aid.
- Schools - New York State - New York City, Miscellaneous, 1957-1972 (Box 230, Folder 2308)
  Appeals for aid.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - Buckley School - NAR Speech - Graduation, 1952 (Box 230, Folder 2311)
  Outline of speech by NAR on purpose and values of people and actions.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - International School of Art, 1949-1970 (Box 230, Folder 2312)
  NAR contributions, 1965-1966. Miscellaneous requests and brochures.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New Lincoln School (formerly Experimental School, Inc.), 1948-1966 (Box 230, Folder 2313)
  Miscellaneous correspondence and brochures. Requests for aid declined. Changed name 3/26/49.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New Lincoln School (formerly Experimental School, Inc.) - Horace Mann, 1931-1948 (Box 230, Folder 2314)
  NAR interest in Parent Teacher Association.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New Lincoln School (formerly Experimental School, Inc.) - Emily A. Barnes Fund, 1937-1959 (Box 231, Folder 2315)
  Fund set up to aid Lincoln School teachers in special circumstances. NAR was the principal contributor. Organization. Administration. Difficulties because of indefinite future of Lincoln School. Extension of funds. Dissolution of fund. Extended account of NAR's involvement in Lincoln School controversy. Minute Book, 1937-1959, Original record copy. Correpondents include NAR, John E. Lockwood, Vera Goeller, G. R. Mirick, Arthur W. Packard.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New Lincoln School (formerly Experimental School, Inc.) - Emily A. Barnes Fund - Distributions, 1938-1959 (Box 231, Folder 2316)
  Letters transmitting gifts to Lincoln School teachers. Letters of acknowledgement.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New Lincoln School (formerly Experimental School, Inc.) - Emily A. Barnes Fund - Recipients, 1937-1952 (Box 231, Folder 2317)
  Contributions, appeals, responses. Management security holdings.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New School for Social Research - General, 1946-1969 (Box 231, Folder 2318)
  Printed material; invitations to speak declined; invitations to serve declined; appeals declined. Correspondence re Alvin Johnson Fund. Correspondents include Bryn Hovde.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New School for Social Research - Contributions, 1947-1949 (Box 232, Folder 2319)
  NAR gifts 1947, 1949. Other appeals declined.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New School for Social Research - NAR Lecture, 1967-1971 (Box 232, Folder 2322)
  Transcript and article NAR's art lecture, 3/15/67. Correspondence, favorable comments, requests for transcript. Requests for contribution to New School Arts Center declined.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - New School for Social Research - Victor Andrade, 1947-1949 (Box 232, Folder 2323)
  NAR's support of Andrade as Visiting Professor at New School for Social Research.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - Union Theological Seminary, 1948-1970 (Box 232, Folder 2324)
  NAR contribution, 1962. Miscellaneous correspondence and requests. Rockefeller Foundation grant of $525,000; 1954.
- Schools - New York State - New York City - United Nations International School, 1949-1966 (Box 232, Folder 2325)
  Established 1949. NAR contributions, 1949, 1966. Rockefeller family contribution.
- Schools - North Carolina, Ohio, Oregon, Pennsylvania, South Carolina, 1947-1970 (Box 232, Folder 2326)
  Miscellaneous requests for aid.
- Schools - Rhode Island, South Dakota, Tennessee, Texas, Utah, Vermont, Virginia, Washington (State), West Virginia, Wisconsin, Wyoming, 1954-1970 (Box 232, Folder 2327)
  Miscellaneous requests for aid. Holy Cross Total Community Service Center Proposal, 10/24/68.
- Schools - Vermont, Virginia - Saxtons River, Vermont Academy, 1954 (Box 232, Folder 2328)
- Schools - Vermont, Virginia - Virginia - The Madeira School, 1957-1969 (Box 232, Folder 2329)
  NAR donations, 1957-1959. Printed material.
- Schools - Vermont, Virginia - Virginia - Virginia Military Institute, 1947-1950 (Box 232, Folder 2330)
  Lexington, VA. Requests for contributions declined.
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - General, 1945-1971 (Box 233, Folder 2331)
  NAR was never a member of any scout troop. National Council of the Boy Scouts of America elected NAR an Honorary Member, 1969. NAR contribution to Boy Scout Development Fund, 1969; to Scouts International Bureau, 1954. Rockefeller Brothers Fund contribution, 1953, 1966.
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Inter-American Advisory Committee on Scouting, 1946 (Box 233, Folder 2332)
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Boy Scouts International Bureau, 1951-1956 (Box 233, Folder 2333)
  NAR gives Scout executive letters of introduction to Latin American leaders. NAR gives $3,000 to Bureau. Plaque given to NAR. Correspondents include NAR, D. C. Spry.
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York City Council - General Correspondence and Contributions, 1947-1971 (Box 233, Folder 2334)
  Certificate of Appreciation issued to NAR, 1947. NAR contributions, 1938-1952. Registration fee, 1952. NAR resigned from Board of Boy Scouts, 4/8/47. Governor and Mrs. NAR served as Honorary Chairmen of the Greater New York Council's Boy Scout Dinner, 1969.
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York City Council - General Correspondence and Contributions, 1947-1971 (Box 233, Folder 2335)
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York City Council - Executive Board, Minutes of Meetings, 1946-1947 (Box 233, Folder 2336)
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Greater New York City Council - Executive Board - NAR's Membership and Resignation - Executive Board, 1946-1947 (Box 233, Folder 2337)
  NAR's acceptance and resignation from the Executive Board.
- Scouting, Boy Scouts of America - Katahdin Area Council, 1954-1960 (Box 233, Folder 2338)
  Bar Harbor, Maine. NAR gave a small donation.
- Scouting, Girl Scouts of America - General, 1947-1970 (Box 233, Folder 2339)
  NAR contribution to the Hudson Valley Girl Scouts Council, 1963.
- Scouting, Girl Scouts of America - National Headquarters, 1947-1964 (Box 233, Folder 2340)
- Scouting, Girl Scouts of America - Westchester County, 1959-1970 (Box 233, Folder 2341)
- Sealantic Fund, 1951-1963 (Box 233, Folder 2342)
  Established in 1939 by John Davison Rockefeller, Jr., to provide a means for extending assistance after his death to certain organizations in Westchester County, New York, and on Mount Desert Island, Maine. (Name is derived from a combination of "Seal" Harbor and Poc-"antic"-o.) The Sealantic Fund was merged with the Rockefeller Brothers Fund in 1973. Correspondence re Sealantic donations to Mount Desert Island Hospital, 1963; American Theological Library Association, 1961; American Association of Theological Schools, 1960; Fort Lee Section of Palisades Interstate Park, 1956. Thanks to John Davison Rockefeller, Jr. and Laurance Spelman Rockefeller. List of Sealantic Fund Trustees in 1951. No NAR correspondence.
- Services, Offers of (A-Z), 1962-1971 (Box 234, Folder 2343)
  General offers to NAR for miscellaneous services.
- Shacter, John, 1958-1960 (Box 234, Folder 2344)
  Sends memo re "Hard Facts & Bold Strategies" and his ideas on national security. Printed matter.
- Shaver, Dorothy, 1940-1958 (Box 234, Folder 2345)
  Friend of NAR. President of Lord & Taylor. Correspondence re American Design Awards, printed material and invitations, John Davison Rockefeller 3rd gets award, NAR on Committee.
- Shell Union Oil Corporation, 1947-1949 (Box 234, Folder 2346)
  NAR declines invitation to Preview "Prospecting for Petroleum." Francis A. Jamieson digest of "The Mounting Cost of Our Traffic Muddle." Graded excellent by NAR.
- Shellaby, Robert K., 1946-1960 (Box 234, Folder 2347)
  Los Angeles editor of "Christian Science Monitor" and friend of NAR. NAR appreciation for his work. Sends printed matter and views of his new job.
- Shelters, Radioactive Fallout, 1962 (Box 234, Folder 2348)
  General information on radioactive fallout. Report, "Fallout Protection for Amherst College." Printed material.
- Silverman, Louis L. (Professor), 1952-1967 (Box 234, Folder 2349)
  Professor at Dartmouth. NAR sent autographed copy of the Godkin Lectures, 1962. Louis L. Silverman tries to interest NAR in proposed civic center in Tel Aviv, NAR declines saying he is already Vice President of the Amun-Israeli Housing Corporation, 1952.
- Slater, Irene J., 1953-1967 (Box 234, Folder 2350)
  In 1967 Miss Slater passed the New York Bar Exam. General correspondence.
- Smith, Alfred E. Memorial Foundation/Governor Smith Memorial Fund - Contributions, 1947-1971 (Box 234, Folder 2351)
  NAR contributions: 1947, 1948-1958, $1,000 yearly; 1959, $1,200; 1960-1966, $1,000 yearly; 1967, $10,186.90; 1968-1971, $1,000 yearly. NAR was guest speaker at Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation Dinner, 1970.
- Smith, Alfred E. Memorial Foundation/Governor Smith Memorial Fund - General, 1946-1960 (Box 234, Folder 2352)
  Governor Smith Memorial; dedication, ground breaking, 10/19/49. John Davison Rockefeller Jr. a member of Memorial Fund Committee in 1949. Text of Address by Vice President Richard M. Nixon, 10/19/56. Alfred E. Smith Memorial Dinner booklets listing guests; 1947-1951, 1954-1955, 1957-1960.
- Smith, Carleton Sprague - General Correspondence, 1945-1960 (Box 235, Folder 2353)
  Re Dr. Smith's cultural center program for Latin America. NAR hired Smith as a consultant in 1946, paid him $735.
- Smithsonian Gallery of Art, 1938-1939 (Box 235, Folder 2354)
  Printed matter. NAR congratulations to Edward Bruce for his work on behalf of "Art In This Country." Re plans for Smithsonian Gallery. Correspondents include Edward Bruce.
- Socialism - General Correspondence, 1949 (Box 235, Folder 2355)
  The trend of socialism. Analysis of strategy, techniques and tactics of leftist groups. Report Fred Eldean Public Relations Counsel, 1949.
- Societies - General (A-Z), 1966-1969 (Box 235, Folder 2356)
  General requests for contributions. NAR contribution to Rensselaer County Historical Society, enrollment as benefactor, 1961; contribution to Memorial Fund, 1963. NAR as a Sponsor of the Tioga County Historical Society, 1965. English Neighborhood Historical Society gave NAR a land deed, (Lot 211, a small tract of land situated in Borough of Leonia, Bergen County, New Jersey), 1963. NAR contribution of $1,000 to the awards dinner of the Society for the Family of Man, 1968.
- Socony-Mobil Oil Company, Inc. (formerly Socony-Vacuum Oil Co.) - General Correspondence, 1947-1964 (Box 235, Folder 2357)
  Incorporated as The Standard Oil Company of New York in 1882, in 1931 it acquired The Vacuum Oil Company. In 1934 Socony-Vacuum Oil Company ceased to be primarily a holding company and took over the direct operations of certain of its properties. In 1955 it became Socony-Mobil Oil Company, Inc. Remarks of B. Brewster Jennings at the annual meeting of stockholders.
- Speeches, Miscellaneous, 1962-1969 (Box 235, Folder 2358)
  Copies of speeches sent to NAR: Senator Frank Church's speech at the Center for Inter-American Relations, Inc. "Foreign Aid Revisited," 1969. Address by His Excellency Maurice Courve de Murville, French Minister of Foreign Affairs, before the 20th Session of the United Nations Assembly, 9/29/65. Address by W. F. Butler, President of the National Association of Business Economists and Vice President of Chase Manhattan Bank, 10/25/62. Raymond C. Firestone, President, Firestone Tire & Company, "National Aims and Business Responsibility," 6/20/62. Thomas L. Hughes, Director of Intelligence and Research, Department of State, "The World Turned Upside Down," 5/19/66.
- Speeches - Requests for Speeches - (A-Z) Miscellaneous, 1968 (Box 235, Folder 2359)
  One request for an NAR speech.